Who?
The Godfather of the Sovereign Sanctum.
The Godfather?
What do you want?
I hear you’ve issued a death threat
to the Four Great Families.
Golantis is under my protection.
You overreach, Godfather.
You take the righteous
path, we walk in blood.
We don't interfere.
You push me, you'll regret it.
So you want to
declare war on me?
Fine!
Then war it is!
As you wish.
Advance the attack on
the Four Great Families immediately!
And declare war
on the Sovereign Sanctum!
The Black Dragon Covenant
won’t let this go.
Then let him try.
Activate maximum protocol.
Exterminate every member of
the Black Dragon Covenant.
Mobilize one hundred thousand Holy
Knights
to strike their stronghold.
Lock onto the Black Dragon's location.
I'm taking his head personally.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
You’re going yourself?
He's too strong.
Only I can handle him.
Calm the guests.
I'll be back soon.
My lord, I’ll be
waiting for our wedding night.
Be ready.
Our child will be a legend.
My lord.